A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.1, Series 100 International - Series 257 Virgin Islands, U.S.A. FA386a
Rockefeller Archive Center
- United States, 1909-1974; 200; 28 Cubic Feet; 69 __Boxes __28 cubic feet
  - United States - Social Sciences, 1921-1971; 200.S; 48 Cubic Feet; 120 __Boxes __48 cubic feet
    - Social Science Research Council - Unemployment Compensation - Report, undated (Box 407, Folder 4823)
    - Social Science Research Council - Unemployment Reserves & Relief, 1933-1935 (Box 408, Folder 4824)
    - Social Science Research Council - Unemployment Reserves & Relief - Report, 1934 (Box 408, Folder 4825)
    - Social Science Research Council - Washington Personnel Office, 1942-1945 (Box 408, Folder 4826)
    - Social Science Research Council - Washington Personnel Office - Reports, 1944-1945; 2 items (Box 408, Folder 4827)
    - Social Science Research Council - Yale Seminar, 1930-1935 (Box 408, Folder 4828)
    - Social Science Research Council - Yale Seminar, 1930-1935 (Box 408, Folder 4829)
    - Social Science Research Council - Yale Seminar, 1930-1935 (Box 408, Folder 4830)
    - Stanford University - Angelo, Homer G. - (International Law), 1953-1955 (Box 408, Folder 4831)
    - Stanford University - Baba, Masao - (Economics), 1954-1955 (Box 408, Folder 4832)
    - Stanford University - Food Research Institute - Davis, Joseph S. - (Economics & Religion), 1952-1955 (Box 408, Folder 4833)
    - Stanford University - Food Research Institute - Zagoroff, S. D. - (Economics), 1953-1954 (Box 408, Folder 4834)
    - Stanford University - Food Research Institute - Zagoroff, S. D. - (Economics) - Reports & Reprints, 1954; 2 items (Box 408, Folder 4835)
    - Stanford University - Sex Adjustment, 1949-1954 (Box 409, Folder 4836)
    - Stanford University - Soviet Law, 1950-1952 (Box 409, Folder 4837)
    - Stanford University - Stuart, Graham H. - (Political Science), 1954-1955 (Box 409, Folder 4838)
    - Swarthmore College - Lindberg, John - (Visit, Economics), 1948-1949 (Box 409, Folder 4839)
    - Swarthmore College - Peace Collection, 1948-1952 (Box 409, Folder 4840)
    - Tolman, Edward G. - (Psychology), 1951-1954 (Box 409, Folder 4841)
    - Tolman, Edward G. - (Psychology) - Report, 1951 (Box 409, Folder 4842)
    - Totalitarian Studies - Holborn, Hajo, 1940 (Box 409, Folder 4843)
    - Tufts College - Halm, George - (Refugee, Economics), 1935-1941 (Box 409, Folder 4844)
    - Tufts College - Sociology, 1944-1951 (Box 409, Folder 4845)
    - Tufts College - Sociology, 1944-1951 (Box 409, Folder 4846)
    - Tufts College - Sociology, 1944-1951 (Box 409, Folder 4847)
    - Tufts College - Sociology - Reprints, 1946-1949; 3 items (Box 409, Folder 4848)
    - Tulane University - Stone, Ferdinand F. - (Travel, Comparative Law), 1954-1955 (Box 409, Folder 4849)
    - Tulane University - Stone, Ferdinand F. - (Travel, Comparative Law) - Reprints, 1947-1954; 3 items (Box 409, Folder 4850)
    - Universities Committee on Postwar International Problems - Harvard University, 1942-1945 (Box 410, Folder 4851)
    - Universities Committee on Postwar International Problems - Harvard University, 1942-1945 (Box 410, Folder 4852)
    - Universities Committee on Postwar International Problems - Harvard University, 1942-1945 (Box 410, Folder 4853)
    - Universities Committee on Postwar International Problems - Harvard University - Reports, 1942-1943; 19 items (Box 410, Folder 4854)
    - Universities Committee on Postwar International Problems - Harvard University - Report, 1943 (Box 410, Folder 4855)
    - Universities Committee on Postwar International Problems - Harvard University - Report, 1943 (Box 410, Folder 4855)
    - Universities Committee on Postwar International Problems - Harvard University - Pamphlets, 1942-1945; 21 items (Box 410, Folder 4856)
    - University of Alabama - Business Research, 1939-1941 (Box 410, Folder 4857)
    - University of Alabama - Business Research - Reports, 1937-1938; 3 items (Box 410, Folder 4858)
    - University of Alabama - Business Research - Reports, 1939; 5 items (Box 410, Folder 4859)
    - University of Alabama - Business Research - Reports, 1940-1941; 2 items (Box 410, Folder 4860)
    - University of Alabama - Business Research - Maps, Undated; 27 items (Box 410, Folder 4861)
    - University of Alabama - Voegelin, Erich - (Refugee, Political Science), 1939-1941 (Box 411, Folder 4862)
    - University of Alabama - Voegelin, Erich - (Refugee, Political Science), 1942 (Box 411, Folder 4863)
    - University of Buffalo - Behrendt, Walter K. - (Refugee, City Planning), 1937-1940 (Box 411, Folder 4864)
    - University of Buffalo - Price Studies, 1942-1943 (Box 411, Folder 4865)
    - University of Buffalo - Price Studies - Reprints, 1943; 2 items (Box 411, Folder 4866)
    - University of Buffalo - Buchanan, Norman S. - (Travel, Economic Development), 1952-1955 (Box 411, Folder 4867)
    - University of California - Carleton, Alford - (Visit, Middle East Seminar), 1953-1954 (Box 411, Folder 4868)
    - University of California - Carleton, Alford - (Visit, Middle East Seminar), 1953-1954 (Box 411, Folder 4868)
    - University of California - Ellis, Howard S. - (Travel, Economics) (Box 411, Folder 4869)
    - University of California - Geddes, Arthur) - (Visit, Geography), 1950-1954 (Box 411, Folder 4870)
    - University of California - Jones, Howard - (Travel, Child Welfare), 1954 (Box 411, Folder 4871)
    - University of California - Kariel, Henry S. - (Legal and Political Philosophy), 1953-1955 (Box 411, Folder 4872)
    - University of California - Minar, David W. - (Legal and Political Philosophy), 1954-1955 (Box 411, Folder 4873)
    - University of Chicago - American Foreign Policy Center, 1950-1955 (Box 411, Folder 4874)
    - University of Chicago - Kennington, Richard H. - (Legal and Political Philosophy), 1954 (Box 411, Folder 4875)
    - University of Chicago - Letwin, Shirley Robin - (British Political Philosophy), 1953-1955 (Box 411, Folder 4876)
    - University of Chicago - Marriage Adjustment, 1938-1940 (Box 411, Folder 4877)
    - University of Chicago - Marriage Adjustment, 1951-1959 (Box 411, Folder 4878)
    - University of Chicago - Marriage Adjustment, 1951-1959 (Box 411, Folder 4879)
    - University of Chicago - Polanyi, Michael - (Social Philosophy), 1951-1952 (Box 412, Folder 4880)
    - University of Chicago - Q-Technique - (Psychology), 1951-1952 (Box 412, Folder 4881)
    - University of Colorado - Ehrmann, Henry W. - (Political Science, LAPP), 1941, 1945-1962 (Box 412, Folder 4882)
    - University of Colorado - Ehrmann, Henry W. - (Political Science, LAPP), 1941, 1945-1962 (Box 412, Folder 4883)
    - University of Colorado - Ehrmann, Henry W. - (Political Science, LAPP), 1941, 1945-1962 (Box 412, Folder 4884)
    - University of Delaware - Income Tax Study, 1939-1945 (Box 412, Folder 4885)
    - University of Delaware - Income Tax Study, 1939-1945 (Box 412, Folder 4886)
    - University of Delaware - Income Tax Study, 1951-1954 (Box 412, Folder 4887)
    - University of Denver - Economics of Nazi Germany, 1941-1942 (Box 412, Folder 4888)
    - University of Denver - Economics of Nazi Germany, 1941-1942 (Box 412, Folder 4889)
    - University of Kansas City - Manheim, Ernst - (Refugee, Sociology), 1937-1940 (Box 412, Folder 4890)
    - University of Kentucky - Vandenbosch, Amry - (Political Science), 1949-1955 (Box 412, Folder 4891)
    - University of Maine - Hinton, Wilfred J. - (Visit, Economics), 1947-1948 (Box 412, Folder 4892)
    - University of Maryland - Lee, Shu-Ching - (Chinese Agriculture Study), 1945-1946 (Box 412, Folder 4893)
    - University of Michigan - Hall, Robert - (Travel, S. America, Geography), 1941-1942 (Box 412, Folder 4894)
    - University of Michigan - Hall, Robert - (Travel, S. America, Geography), 1941-1942 (Box 412, Folder 4895)
    - University of Michigan - Hall, Robert - (Travel, S. America, Geography) - Report, 1942 (Box 412, Folder 4896)
    - University of Michigan - Human Behavior, 1952-1955 (Box 413, Folder 4897)
    - University of Michigan - Investments, 1946-1947, 1950 (Box 413, Folder 4898)
    - University of Michigan - Investments, 1946-1947, 1950 (Box 413, Folder 4899)
    - University of Michigan - Research Center for Group Dynamics, 1949-1955 (Box 413, Folder 4900)
    - University of Michigan - Research Center for Group Dynamics, 1949-1955 (Box 413, Folder 4901)
    - University of Michigan - Research Center for Group Dynamics, 1949-1955 (Box 413, Folder 4902)
    - University of Michigan - Survey Research Center, 1948-1955 (Box 413, Folder 4903)
    - University of Michigan - Survey Research Center, 1948-1955 (Box 413, Folder 4904)
    - University of Michigan - Survey Research Center, 1948-1955 (Box 413, Folder 4905)
    - University of Michigan - Survey Research Center, 1948-1955 (Box 413, Folder 4906)
    - University of Michigan - Survey Research Center - Reprints & Pamphlets, 1948-1951; 2 items (Box 413, Folder 4907)
    - University of Michigan - Survey Research Center - Labor Organizations, 1952-1958 (Box 413, Folder 4908)
    - University of Michigan - Survey Research Center - Labor Organizations, 1952-1958 (Box 413, Folder 4909)
    - University of Michigan - Survey Research Center - Labor Organizations, 1952-1958 (Box 413, Folder 4910)
    - University of Michigan - Survey Research Center - Labor Organizations - Reprints & Pamphlets, 1947-1958; 8 items (Box 413, Folder 4911)
    - University of Michigan - War Seminar, 1940-1943 (Box 414, Folder 4912)
    - University of Michigan - War Seminar, 1940-1943 (Box 414, Folder 4913)
    - University of Michigan - War Seminar - Reports & Reprints, 1941; 3 items (Box 414, Folder 4914)
    - University of Minnesota - Cooperman, David - (Legal & Political Philosophy), 1953-1955 (Box 414, Folder 4915)
    - University of Minnesota - Festinger, Leon - (Travel, Preventative Medicine), 1951-1953 (Box 414, Folder 4916)
    - University of Notre Dame - Francis, E. K. - (Travel, Sociology), 1953-1956 (Box 414, Folder 4917)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Fisher, Waldo E. - (Industrial Relations), 1953-1954 (Box 414, Folder 4918)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Mishkin, Paul J. - (Legal & Political Philosophy), 1954-1955 (Box 414, Folder 4919)
    - University of Texas - Witherspoon, Joseph P., Jr. - (Legal & Political Philosophy), 1953-1957 (Box 414, Folder 4920)
    - University of Virginia - Wright, David McCord - (Travel, Industrial Relations), 1953-1955 (Box 414, Folder 4921)
    - University of Wisconsin - Income Tax Study, April 1939-1942 (Box 414, Folder 4922)
    - University of Wisconsin - Income Tax Study, April 1939-1942 (Box 414, Folder 4923)
    - University of Wisconsin - Income Tax Study, April 1939-1942 (Box 414, Folder 4924)
    - University of Wisconsin - Income Tax Study, April 1939-1942 (Box 414, Folder 4925)
    - University of Wisconsin - Income Tax Study - Reports, 1940-1941; 2 items (Box 414, Folder 4926)
    - University of Wisconsin - Kolb, J. H. - (Travel, Rural Sociology), 1948-1950 (Box 415, Folder 4927)
    - University of Wisconsin - Munch, Peter A. - (Visit, Rural Sociology), 1948-1949 (Box 415, Folder 4928)
    - Warner, W. Lloyd - (Travel, Anthropology), 1949-1950 (Box 415, Folder 4929)
    - Wesleyan University - Neumann, Sigmund - (Refugee, Political Science), 1934-1939 (Box 415, Folder 4930)
    - Wesleyan University - Neumann, Sigmund - (Refugee, Political Science), 1954-1958 (Box 415, Folder 4931)
    - World Peace Foundation - Bibliography, 1947-1950 (Box 415, Folder 4932)
    - World Peace Foundation - Bibliography - Reports, 1947; 4 items (Box 416, Folder 4933)
    - World Peace Foundation - Canada - American Conference, 1951-1952 (Box 416, Folder 4934)
    - World Peace Foundation - Document Series, 1948-1952 (Box 416, Folder 4935)
    - World Peace Foundation - Publication, 1946-1954 (Box 416, Folder 4936)
    - World Peace Foundation - Publication, 1946-1954 (Box 416, Folder 4937)
    - Yale University - Bakke, E.W. - (Travel, Industrial Relations), 1953 (Box 416, Folder 4938)
    - Yale University - Books for Indonesia, 1948-1951 (Box 416, Folder 4939)
    - Yale University - Holborn, Hajo - (Refugee, History), 1934-1940 (Box 416, Folder 4940)
    - Yale University - International Relations, 1931-1943 (Box 416, Folder 4941)
    - Yale University - International Relations, 1931-1943 (Box 416, Folder 4942)
    - Yale University - International Relations, 1931-1943 (Box 416, Folder 4943)
    - Yale University - International Relations, 1931-1943 (Box 416, Folder 4944)
    - Yale University - International Relations, 1931-1943 (Box 416, Folder 4945)
    - Yale University - International Relations, 1931-1943 (Box 416, Folder 4946)
    - Yale University - International Relations, 1944-1954 (Box 417, Folder 4947)
    - Yale University - International Relations, 1944-1954 (Box 417, Folder 4948)
    - Yale University - International Relations, 1944-1954 (Box 417, Folder 4949)
    - Yale University - International Relations, 1944-1954 (Box 417, Folder 4950)
    - Yale University - International Relations, 1944-1954 (Box 417, Folder 4951)
    - Yale University - International Relations - Annual Report, 1936-1942 (Box 417, Folder 4952)
    - Yale University - International Relations - Annual Report, 1936-1942 (Box 417, Folder 4953)
    - Yale University - International Relations - Annual Report, 1936-1942 (Box 417, Folder 4954)
    - Yale University - International Relations - Annual Report, 1936-1942 (Box 417, Folder 4955)
    - Yale University - International Relations - Annual Report, 1936-1942 (Box 417, Folder 4956)
    - Yale University - International Relations - Annual Report, 1936-1942 (Box 417, Folder 4957)
    - Yale University - International Relations - Annual Report, 1936-1942 (Box 417, Folder 4958)
    - Yale University - International Relations - Annual Report, 1943-1950 (Box 418, Folder 4959)
    - Yale University - International Relations - Annual Report, 1943-1950 (Box 418, Folder 4960)
    - Yale University - International Relations - Annual Report, 1943-1950 (Box 418, Folder 4961)
    - Yale University - International Relations - Annual Report, 1943-1950 (Box 418, Folder 4962)
    - Yale University - International Relations - Annual Report, 1943-1950 (Box 418, Folder 4963)
    - Yale University - International Relations - Annual Report, 1943-1950 (Box 418, Folder 4964)
    - Yale University - International Relations - Annual Report, 1943-1950 (Box 418, Folder 4965)
    - Yale University - International Relations - Program Statement, 1941 (Box 418, Folder 4966)
    - Yale University - International Relations - Reports, 1934-1935, 1938; 4 items contained in folders 4967-4969. (Box 418, Folder 4967)
    - Yale University - International Relations - Reports, 1934-1935, 1938; 4 items contained in folders 4967-4969. (Box 418, Folder 4968)
    - Yale University - International Relations - Reports, 1934-1935, 1938; 4 items contained in folders 4967-4969. (Box 418, Folder 4969)
    - Yale University - International Relations - Reports, 1943-1950; 4 items (Box 418, Folder 4970)
    - Yale University - Kertesz, Stephen D. - (Political Science), 1948-1950 (Box 418, Folder 4971)
    - Yale University - Kessler, Friedrich - (Refugee, Law), 1935-1939 (Box 418, Folder 4972)
    - Yale University - Kroner, Richard - (Refugee, Logic & Metaphysics), 1940 (Box 418, Folder 4973)
    - Yale University - Labor Management Center, 1945-1946 (Box 418, Folder 4974)
    - Yale University - Labor Management Center, 1947-1951 (Box 419, Folder 4975)
    - Yale University - Labor Management Center, 1947-1951 (Box 419, Folder 4976)
    - Yale University - Labor Management Center - Reports, 1945-1946; 4 items (Box 419, Folder 4977)
    - Yale University - Loewenstein, Karl - (Refugee, Political Science), 1933-1936 (Box 419, Folder 4978)
    - Yale University - Neuner, Robert - (Refugee, Law), 1938-1941 (Box 419, Folder 4979)
    - Yale University - Neuner, Robert - (Refugee, Law), 1942 (Box 419, Folder 4980)
    - Yale University - Mixed Arbital Tribunals, 1937-1939, 1948 (Box 419, Folder 4981)
    - Yale University - Mixed Arbital Tribunals, 1937-1939, 1948 (Box 419, Folder 4982)
    - Yale University - Postwar Studies, 1942-1947 (Box 419, Folder 4983)
    - Yale University - Postwar Studies, 1942-1947 (Box 419, Folder 4984)
    - Yale University - Postwar Studies, 1942-1947 (Box 419, Folder 4985)
    - Yale University - Postwar Studies, 1942-1947 (Box 419, Folder 4986)
    - Yale University - Sherif, Muzafer - (Psychology), 1947-1949 (Box 419, Folder 4987)
    - Yale University - Soerjotjondro, Raden Soejono - (Visit, International Relations), March 1949-April 1951 (Box 419, Folder 4988)
    - Yale University - Soerjotjondro, Raden Soejono - (Visit, International Relations), June 1950-April 1951 (Box 419, Folder 4989)
    - Yale University - Wu, Wen-Tsao - (Visit, Sociology), 1950-1952 (Box 419, Folder 4990)
- Alabama, 1927-1955; 201; 2.5 Cubic Feet; 5 __Boxes __2.5 cubic feet
  International Health Division Correspondence with the state board of health. Reports on tuberculosis, malaria, hookworm. Most material dates from the 1930's.
  There are 6 subseries as follows:
  201 (no program letter, general material which does not fit into a particular program area)
  201 H Hookworm
  201 I Malaria
  201 J Public health demonstrations
  201 Q Epidemiological investigations and studies
  201 T Tuberculosis
  - Health, 1928-1939 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Health, 1928-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Health, 1928-1939 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Health, 1928-1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Health, 1928-1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Health, 1928-1939 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Nutrition, 1939-1942 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Nutrition, 1939-1942 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Nutrition, 1939-1942 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Rabies Study, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Rabies Study, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Rabies Study, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Rabies Study, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Rabies Study, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Rabies Study, 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Rabies Study, 1938-1955 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Rabies Study, 1938-1955 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Rabies Study, 1938-1955 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Rabies Study, 1938-1955 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Rabies Study, 1938-1955 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Rabies Study, 1938-1955 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Rabies Study, 1938-1955 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Rabies Study, 1938-1955 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Rabies Study, 1938-1955 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Rabies Study, 1938-1955 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Rabies Study, 1938-1955 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Rabies Study, 1938-1955 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Rabies Study, 1938-1955 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Rabies Study, 1938-1955 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Rabies Study - Report, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Alabama - Hookworm, 201.H
    - PUT-20 Putnam, Persis] "...Hookworm Infestation Incidence and Intensity in Alabama", 1930 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Alabama - Malaria, 201.I
    - GIL-1 Gill, D. E. "Plasmochin in Malaria Prevention, Experiments in Alabama", 1930-1931 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - GRA-11 Graham, A. H. "Malaria Memoranda", 1927 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Alabama - Public Health Demonstrations, 201.J
    - (Health District), 1937-1941 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - (Health District), 1937-1941 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Alabama - Epidemiological Investigations and Studies, 201.Q
    - Lee County, 1929-July 1936 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Lee County, 1929-July 1936 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Lee County, 1929-July 1936 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Lee County, 1929-July 1936 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Lee County, 1929-July 1936 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Lee County, 1929-July 1936 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Lee County, 1929-July 1936 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Lee County, 1929-July 1936 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Lee County, 1929-July 1936 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Lee County, August 1936-1941 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Lee County, August 1936-1941 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Lee County, August 1936-1941 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Lee County, August 1936-1941 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Lee County, August 1936-1941 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Lee County, August 1936-1941 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Lee County, August 1936-1941 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Lee County, August 1936-1941 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Lee County, August 1936-1941 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Typhus Fever Study, 1932-1936 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Typhus Fever Study, 1932-1936 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Typhus Fever Study, 1932-1936 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Alabama - Tuberculosis, 201.T
    - GRA-1 Graham, A. H. "Some Phases of the Epidemiology of Rural Tuberculosis.", 1936 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - LEE-1 Lee County "Present Status of the Lee County Tuberculosis Project.", 1937 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - PUT-1 Putnam, Persis "... Epidemiology of Tuberculosis in Lee County, Alabama.", 1937 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - PUT-2 Putnam, Persis "Methods Employed in Sampling Clinic Records...", 1937 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - PUT-3 Putnam, Persis "Frequency of Tuberculosis...Revealed by Clinic Diagnostic Procedure.", 1938 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - PUT-4 Putnam, Persis "Spread of Tuberculosis Infection in Rural White & Negro Families of Alabama.", 1938 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Alaska, 1929-1958; 202; 0.5 Cubic Feet; 1 __Box __0.5 cubic feet
  Two subseries, as follows:
  202 D Natural sciences and agriculture
  202 R Humanities and arts
  - Alaska - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 202.D
    - Alaska College of Agriculture and School of Mines - (Auroral Study), 1929-1939 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Alaska College of Agriculture and School of Mines - (Auroral Study), 1929-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Alaska College of Agriculture and School of Mines - (Auroral Study) - Pamphlets, 1935; 2 Items (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alaska - Humanities and Arts, 202.R
    - University of Alaska - History, 1934-1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - University of Alaska - History, 1934-1958 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - University of Alaska - History, 1934-1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - University of Alaska - History, 1934-1958 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - University of Alaska - History, 1934-1958 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- California, 1921-1971; 205; 11 Cubic Feet; 28 __Boxes __11 cubic feet
  Mostly 1930's and 1940's, reflects general foundation program in this period. 205D (natural science) section particularly interesting.
  Nine subseries as follows:
  205 (no program letter, general material which does not fit into a particular program area)
  205 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings)
  205 C Nursing (nursing education, public health nursing)
  205 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture)
  205 L Public health education (schools of hygiene and public health)
  205 M Respiratory diseases 205 R Humanities and arts
  205 S Social sciences
  205 V Virus studies
  - Jaundice, 1943-December 1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Jaundice, 1943-December 1944 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Jaundice, 1943-December 1944 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Stanford University - Brandt, Karl - (Travel, Agricultural Economics), 1947-1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Stanford University - Brandt, Karl - (Travel, Agricultural Economics) - Reports, 1949; 4 Items (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Syphilis, 1938-1943 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Syphilis, 1938-1943 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Syphilis, 1938-1943 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Syphilis, 1938-1943 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Syphilis, 1938-1943 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Syphilis, 1938-1943 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Syphilis - Reports, 1940-1942; 5 items contained in folders 12-13. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Syphilis - Reports, 1940-1942; 5 items contained in folders 12-13. (Box 1, Folder 13)